{
  "chapter": 15,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Content Delivery Network is developed based upon the principle of",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Delivery management",
        "Network planning",
        "Data replication",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The additional content servers in CDN placed at different geographic locations are known as",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Origin server",
        "Edge server",
        "Content server",
        "Source server"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Partial-site replication policy is followed in CDN while web pages include",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Only dynamic content",
        "Only static content",
        "Static and dynamic content",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "User-requested content is always delivered to users from the origin server of content.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Content consumers remain unaware about the use of the CDN service by content providers.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "A content provider can use the services of more than one CDN operator to deliver its content.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Not possible",
        "Possible in some cases",
        "Always possible",
        "Depends upon content type"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The placement of edge servers mainly depend on",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Location of content providers",
        "Geographic locations of users",
        "Availability of space",
        "policy of CDN operator"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Content is automatically distributed to edge servers whenever added to origin server using",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Push technique",
        "Pull technique",
        "Both push and pull techniques",
        "Distribution technique"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following cloud service providers has its own CDN service?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Amazon", "Microsoft", "Google", "All of these"],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "The use of content delivery network is required for",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reducing network traffic",
        "Instantaneous delivery of content",
        "Server load balancing",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    }
  ]
}
